Before AI and AI agents, we were really
used to deterministic code. We know what
the output is when we give it certain
input. But that's not the case anymore.
It is dangerous because then we're going
to make decisions about a product or a
feature or even our just day-to-day
workflow that are based on this one
isolated example. That [music] is just
an anecdote. So it's very important for
us to work with evals that actually
statistically measure how well we're
doing on a population.
>> [music]
>> And there are of course many different
things that affect that number um or or
that eval score. One of which is the
model itself, the underlying model, how
good the the LLM is at being able to
perform that task. But of course, there
are a bunch of other things um such as
the prompt you use, the context you
provide, and things like that that you
know that give the LLM a better chance
of success. what um we'll jump into that
in a little bit more depth. In terms of
the eval, what does the what what do
your evalues look like for this for this
report that we that we released?
>> Yeah, good question. So, what we did was
we um generated a data set, an
evaluation data set.
>> Yeah.
>> That consists of pairs of a question, a
coding question [clears throat]
>> and uh a criteria for evaluation. Mhm.
>> But these questions, they're not just
they don't come from thin air. We
actually take an existing library, open
source library, and we use an agent to
analyze this library and then generate
the question based on the real API of
this library, both the question and the
evaluation criteria. Um and we focus on
questions
um that have to do with the so the
coding task the nature of the coding
task is that it tries to evaluate
someone's a person's or or an agent's
ability to use a library efficiently and
correctly. Mhm.
>> Um so it's less
you know the typical coding tasks that
agents are used to are sort of like lead
code style you know gener like um
implement from scratch something like
bread for search or that sort of task.
This is not it. This is more of a oh you
have paidantic
>> pantic python library um now use pyantic
to generate that sort of class with that
sort of validation you know. Um so it's
it's more about it's more focused on
using the library.
>> Yeah.
>> Um so yeah so that's the data set and
then we um in order to evaluate a method
we ask it to solve the question
>> and then separately we use an agent as a
judge
>> to uh evaluate the solution based on the
criteria that we previously generated.
>> Right. Right.
>> So and the criteria is all about how the
API was used.
>> Gotcha. So, so your tests are twofold
then. Your tests are essentially this is
the challenge and then this is what I
expect. This is how your criteria is
this is how I expect a correct solution
to kind of like you know it needs to use
this library. It needs to use this
method on the library perhaps it needs
to pass this information and we need to
be able to see this kind of outcome. So,
it still allows the the LLM to be
creative in whatever ways it wants to
>> code it, but it needs to hit those
several things which, pardon me, it
needs to hit those several things which
um which require that correct use of the
library. Um, okay. What What are the So,
when things go good, they go good, you
get a pass. When things go bad, what are
the kind of things that we're looking
for? I can I can already guess things
like you know that hallucination of the
API that doesn't exist maybe very often
because it's actually picking the wrong
version of the API. I is that a common
thing? What what are the things that we
look for in failures?
>> Yeah. Um so yeah what you mentioned with
the versions happens uh for sure. Pantic
actually that I mentioned already is a
good example of this because pyantic
version two is quite different to
pyantic version version one and LLMs
often confuse it.
>> Um
>> but also we have I think there is a more
fundamental problem which is uh new or
or private libraries right things that
might not be in the training in the
pre-training data of uh the LLM. there
is no pre-existing knowledge about this.
>> Um, and now suddenly
>> you're asked to use this library, but
you don't know anything about it. So the
if it's an agent, so if it's an LLM,
it's just going to hallucinate. If it's
an agent, it might do web search, it
might read documentation and so on, but
this is quite expensive, quite a lengthy
process, and it might not find what it
needs because some libraries are not
that well documented. Yeah. So niche
libraries, not well-known libraries,
libraries that have a smaller community,
maybe an academic community behind them,
you know, things like this, they're
going to be overlooked.
>> Yeah.
>> And not to mention private libraries
where there is no pre-existing knowledge
and you might not be able to
>> access that much knowledge about them.